Hello friends, I hope you are well.
Welcome to the Mbaoz channel. In the previous video,
we talked about the Master HTTP VPN Rail project, which I taught you how to run
on your Android phone in the easiest way possible.
But many of you
asked me how to download it from GitHub on the national internet.
When I go to the release section and
try to download the files, nothing
happens?
And you got into trouble.  To solve this problem,
you need a site.  A mirror that provides
you with links to GitHub and GitHub projects
.  I want a site.   Let me
introduce you.  There is also another domain called
espan.ir that you can
visit.  It doesn't matter that I'm from Iran.   I
use it.  I will post the link on my Telegram channel
so you can access it more easily
.  Now let's go to GitHub.
Find the GitHub profile name.
Where is the name GitHub?  Where is the name of the GitHub profile or
creator of this project?  You can see it here after
github.com.  Or if
I come down here, it's next to my GitHub icon
.  Let me copy this from the L section
and take it to this git.ir. I'll paste it here. I'll click the
search option
and select the desired user name. Now we have
access to all of his projects. I'll
select the project we want. You can see all of the project content
and download it. Now
you can go to the bottom of the page and
see the attached files here. Click on it and download it according
to the platform you're using and the architecture of
your phone.  The
server is currently being checked
for download and it is running at a good speed
.  I hope you like this video too
.  If this problem is solved, please like and share it
with your friends so that
more people can solve the problem and
connect through this method.  Until the next video,
goodbye.  Yes.